<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array
        name="charlton_string_array">

        <item><![CDATA[
        Charlton Heston is awesome.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        Charles was in an amazing amount of films, spanning from 1950 to 2003 and starred in everything from historical epics to science fiction blockbusters.  Roger Ebert remarked upon an impressive fact about Heston, saying \"Heston made at least three movies that almost everybody eventually sees: <i>Ben-Hur</i>, <i>The Ten Commandments</i> and <i>Planet of the Apes</i>.\"
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        Apart from being a film actor, Charlton Heston was also a civil rights activist, quite notably with his support of the Civil Rights Act of 1964 (the ending of segregation).  Heston picketed several segregated restaurants in Oklahoma City and even marched with Martin Luther King Jr. in Washington, DC.  Charlton stated that he was a civil activist \"long before Hollywood found it fashionable.\"
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        My favorite Heston movie is <font color="#86b5d9"><u>Planet of the Apes</u></font>.  Almost any time Charles is talking during the movie it is pure greatness.  The movie begins with an awesome monologue and ends with a great revelation.  The sequels are good as well, but they are a different kind of good.  Heston makes only a brief (but amazing) appearance in the second film.  If you are going to watch only one Charlton Heston movie, this is the one you want to see.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        Another favorite is <font color="#86b5d9"><u>Ben-Hur</u></font>.  You can tell this movie was made during a different age as soon as it begins because it opens with an Overture.  Filmed in ultra widescreen (2.76 : 1), the film won a record 11 Academy Awards, which has only been matched recently by <i>Titanic</i> and <i>The Return of the King</i>.  Most impressive to me is the chariot sequence, which still holds up as an impressive action scene even today.  It is especially fantastic when you realize that they created this scene without the use of any computers.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        Tap here to read more about <font color="#86b5d9"><u>Charlton Heston</u></font> on Wikipedia.
        ]]></item>

    </string-array>
</resources>