<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array
        name="stats_info_string_array">

        <item><![CDATA[
        The <b><u>Summary</u></b> tab displays a quick glance of a player\'s win percentage for public and ranked games.  It also contains a list of all known matches for this player.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        The <b><u>Favorites</u></b> tab uses both Public and Ranked matches in its calculations.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        The <b><u>Success</u></b> tab uses both Public and Ranked matches in its calculations and only considers heroes that have been played in at least 1% of matches.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        The <b><u>Ranked</u></b> and <b><u>Public</u></b> tabs have many more statistics than the Summary tab.  Only games that lasted more than five minutes are used in any statistics calculations!
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        The <b><u>Other</u></b> tab contains statistics for all matches not used in the <b>Public</b> and <b>Ranked</b> tabs.  This includes matches that were excluded because they are less than five minutes long.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        The <b><u>All Heroes</u></b> tab displays a list of all heroes you have played in any Public or Ranked match.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        <b><u>KDA</u></b> represents the player\'s average <b>K</b>ills, <b>D</b>eaths, and <b>A</b>ssists per game.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        <b><u>K/D</u></b> represents the player\'s average number of <b>K</b>ills divided by the average number of <b>D</b>eaths per game.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        <b><u>K+A/D</u></b> represents the player\'s average number of <b>K</b>ills and <b>A</b>ssists divided by the average number of <b>D</b>eaths per game.
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        <i>The score values below are experimental.  They are intended to give insight into different aspects of a player\'s match history.</i>
        ]]></item>

        <item><![CDATA[
        The <b><u>CS Score</u></b> represents the average combined CS (last hits + denies) of all ten players in each game.
        ]]></item>

        <!--<item><![CDATA[-->
        <!--The <b><u>GPM Score</u></b> represents the average combined GPM for all players in each game.-->
        <!--]]></item>-->

        <!--<item><![CDATA[-->
        <!--The <b><u>XPM Score</u></b> represents the average combined XPM for all players in each game.-->
        <!--]]></item>-->

        <!--<item><![CDATA[-->
        <!--The <b><u>Composite Score</u></b> is the combined total of the GPM and XPM Scores.-->
        <!--]]></item>-->

        <item><![CDATA[
        The <b><u>Teamwork Score</u></b> is the average number of people involved in each kill on the player\'s team.
        ]]></item>

    </string-array>
</resources>